<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jacob Hernandez</title>
    <link>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jacob Hernandez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: 5 Star Restaurant Review Classifier</title>
      <link>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Scrapped restuarant reviews along with their ratings were scrapped of Trip Advisor. Built a model using Tensorflow and tuned its hyperparameters with WandB (Weights and Biases) Built a client facing Streamlit web app deployed through heroku that makes API calls to Flask server hosted on Google Cloud Run    Link to GitHub Repository
Link to Web App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Financial Dashboard and Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>This web app is comprised of three different dashboards:
 Stock Financials and Fundementals Wall street bets and twitter sentiment analaysis Twitter Sentiment Analaysis    Link to GitHub Repository
Link to Web App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Film Box Office Revenue Model</title>
      <link>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Production companies and studios alike always aim for the biggest budget often disregarding creative integrity. Often times these studios resort to uncreative ideas like reboots, endless sequels, and book adaptations. These attempts are often seen as a cash grab to the more savy film audience. This projects delves deeper into what characteristics correlate with higher box office revenues. The data for this project is scrapped of Wikipedia so take these results with a grain of salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: KNearest Neighbor SPY Direction Model</title>
      <link>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jacobh310.github.io/Jacob_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Created a KNN Model that gives a buy or pass signal (Precision 0.56)
  Collected daily price data (Open,Close,High,Low,Volume) for SPY, E-MINI, and VIX on finance.yahoo.com
  Engineered techinal common indicators and created own moving average ratios
  Optimized KNN model with over 100 features. Used the precision recall curve to optimize the threshold value
  Tested model in a trading simulated envirment for profit/loss evaluation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
